rc-fever.com 2010-06-06

# Privacy Notice : Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**  

  * This policy covers how Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com treats personal information that Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com does not own or control, or to people that Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com does not employ or manage. In addition, certain Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com associated companies such as [SanDisk](http://www.sandisk.com/) and [Sony](http://www.sony.com/) have their own privacy statements which can be viewed by clicking on the links. 

**Information Collection and Use**

**General**  

  * Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com collects personal information when you register with Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com, when you use Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com products or services, when you visit Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com pages or the pages of certain Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 
  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. For some financial products and services we may also ask for your address, Social Security number, and information about your assets. Once you register with Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer. 
  * Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com cookie information, and the page you request. 
  * Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

**Children**  

  * When a child under age 13 attempts to register with Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com, we ask that he or she have a parent or guardian create a Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com Account to obtain parental permission. 
  * Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com will not contact children under age 13 about special offers or for marketing purposes without a parent's permission. 
  * Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com does not ask a child under age 13 for more personal information, as a condition of participation, than is reasonably necessary to participate in a given activity or promotion. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  

  * Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 
    * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com communicate with you about offers from Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 
    * We have a parent's permission to share the information if the user is a child under age 13. Parents have the option of allowing Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com to collect and use their child's information without consenting to Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com sharing of this information with people and companies who may use this information for their own purposes; 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
    * We transfer information about you if Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 
  * Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area. 
    * Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 
    * Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies). 

**Cookies**  

  * Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com may set and access Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com cookies on your computer. 
  * Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com's cookies. 

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

**General**  

  * You can edit your [Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com Account Information](http://www.rc-fever.com/index.php?main_page=account) at any time. 
  * New categories of marketing communications may be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive. 
  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com Newsletter, that are considered part of your Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. 

**Confidentiality and Security**  

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  

  * Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Buy Align, ESky, Walkera, Skyartec RC Toys at RC-Fever.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**Questions and Suggestions**  

  * If you have questions or suggestions, please complete a [feedback form](http://www.rc-fever.com/index.php?main_page=contact_us) or you can contact us at:
